tvarticles.org 2019-07-18

# Privacy Policy |

### **Who we are**

TvArticles is an online portal where you can read updates on Indian TV Shows online of Star Plus, Zee TV, Sony TV, Colors TV, Sab TV, Star Bharat, & TV and more. Our website address is: [http://www.tvarticles.org](http://www.tvarticles.org/).

If you would like to contact us regarding any queries or feedback, please feel free to do so by using the [Contact Us](http://www.tvarticles.org/contact-us/) option located at the top of the page. You can also tell us your opinion or engage in discussions about any episode by using our Leave a Reply box or the Facebook Comments box located at the end of each post.

TvArticles cares about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following terms to learn more about our privacy policy. By registering to and creating account at Play-Kardo.com you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.

### **What personal data we collect and why we collect it**

**Comments**

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

**Media**

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

**Contact forms**

Our site uses a contact us form located at the top of the page to help users inform us about their opinions or to inform us about any problem that they are facing on our site. We do not use the information submitted through the contact us form for any marketing purposes. The data that you submit through the contact us form is kept for a certain period for customer service purposes only and is disposed of after the issue has been resolved.

**Cookies**

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

**Embedded content from other websites**

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

**Analytics**

We use Google Analytics, which is covered by [**Google’s Privacy policy**](http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy.html).

### **Who we share your data with**

We will never sell your personal information, or use it for any other purpose other than logging in/out, demographics for our knowledge, and any voluntary feature of the site.

### **How long we retain your data**

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

### **What rights you have over your data**

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

### **Where we send your data**

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

### **Your contact information**

If you contact us using our contact us form you will be contacting us privately and your private information will not be visible to anyone except us.

### **Additional Information**

  * We will never sell your personal information, or use it for any other purpose other than logging in/out, demographics for our knowledge, and any voluntary feature of the site.
  * We use cookies with minimal information in them.
  * We use Google Analytics, which is covered by **[Google’s Privacy policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy.html)**.
  * We allow you to contact other members via profile pages, but no private information is sent unless you want them to see. (you can choose not receive any communication from anyone.)
  * If you are below 13 then you can NOT use this forum. Do NOT register if you are below the age of 13.
  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website.
  * Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting **[Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/)**. (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting **[aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/)**.)

If you have not **[opted out of third-party ad serving](https://www.google.com/support/dfp_sb/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=94152)** , the cookies of other **[third-party vendors or ad networks](https://www.google.com/support/dfp_sb/bin/answer.py?answer=94149)** may also be used to serve ads on your site, and should be disclosed in your privacy policy as well in the following manner.

  * Notify your site visitors of the third-party vendors and ad networks serving ads on your site.
  * Provide links to the appropriate vendor and ad network websites.
  * Inform your users that they may visit those websites to opt out of the use of cookies for interest-based advertising (if the vendor or ad network offers this capability). Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of some third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting **[aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/)**.

Because publisher sites and laws across countries vary, we’re unable to suggest specific privacy policy language. However, you may wish to review resources such as the **[Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)** for guidance on drafting a privacy policy.

**In detail**

  1. **What does TvArticles Privacy Policy cover?**  
All the personal information we collect is noted on your profile page. That includes your name, email, date of birth and biographic information. The personal information that you provide is used for Registration purpose. In order for you to participate in TvArticles discussion you must complete a registration form. As part of registration form, we require your email address.
  2. **Profile Information**  
TvArticles allow other users to browse your full name, instant messaging URL, and other details within your member profile should you provide this optional information. TvArticles allows for the RSS syndication of all of its public content within the website.
  3. **Cookies**  
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser in order to check in if you are logged in or out. All the other information is located in TvArticles server. Some of our business partners may use cookies on our website (for example advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.
  4. **Third-party Advertisement**  
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit **[networkadvertising.org](http://networkadvertising.org/)**.
  5. **Membership Validity**  
We reserve the right to delete any message, ban any member for any or no reason whatsoever. Members found to be abusing the contact form, using it for commercial purposes, or otherwise breaking the Community Guidelines will have his/her membership suspended.
  6. **Children below 13 DO NOT Register**  
The Federal Trade Commission’s Children Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA) require that Web Sites are to obtain parental consent before collecting, using, or disclosing personal information from children under 13. If you are below 13 then you cannot use this forum. Do NOT register if you are below the age of 13.
